Move, move, quickly!
To the position of the four battalions!
Get the burnt box!\NHurry up!
Team 1 is ready!
How many shots are coming?
I think 20 shots.
Son of bitches..
We'll pay you back with 50 shots\Ncounter fire!
50 menace shots, fire!
- Fire!\N- Fire!
How many shots?
Two hundred shots.
These bastards..
Just go over 500 shots.
Chief of staff!
I think it's 100 shots this time!
Are they crazy?\NAre they going to war?
Blow 200 shots!
A few years ago, the front unit, which had been pierced in knock order, was pierced again.
It's broke.\NMilitary discipline is broken.
Is the military an army these days?You have to roll it.
-Bang!\N-Bang!
- It's a perfect day!\N- Good day!
- Hello!\N- Hello!
- Here, here, here!\N-Hello
-Bang!\N- Now, even the lucky lottery!
-Bang!\N- Thank you!
Hey, what's the sound?\NStill in a war?
The North is continuing to shoot and provoke, perhaps because of an accident in Cheorwon.
Hey, I'm on my way.
Don't back down. Push it according to the rules of engagement.
You're wasting your ammo, you punks.
So far, 3,000 shots have been fired.
Give me another 300 shots.
The second round is on me.
The 2nd round is...
It's today's mission.
Captain's on his way, you know?
Captain, there're three horse dungs, three.
Go and see where it's coming from. Go!
Can sergeant Park talk to dogs?
Where are you?
500m?
300m?\NOK!
Hey, get ready.
- Loyalty!\N- Loyalty!
- Park Chunwoo! Park Chunwoo!\N- Park Chunwoo! Park Chunwoo!
- Park Chunwoo!\N- Park Chunwoo! Park Chun...
Holstein, about 18 months.
- He's stressed out.\N- He's stressed out.
It's a bit fishy.
- Holstein, Holstein!\N- Hols!
Ayrshire.
Airsher, airsher!\NIt's Airsher!
Sergeant Park, you're amazing.
Isn't he like a milk barista?
My house used to have a big ranch.
- Ranch?\N- Ranch.
Why do you forget about the foot-and-mouth disease?
Loyalty!
- Hey, Seongho!\N- Yes.
Not going to work, huh?
Hey, if knock defect is coming again you know?\NGet moving!
- I got it!\N- Hey, hey.
Let's clean this up. Let's go clean up our area!
- Yes, sir!\N- Got it!
Come on.
- Move quickly, move, move.
- Yes, sir\N- Yes, sir.
Supply officer, are you on duty?
No, it looks like the hols's stuck again.
It's not easy to get water.
- Take care of yourself. Thank you.
- Good day.\N- Good luck!
- Hey, bring me the chessboard.\N- Yes, sir.
- How many days are left?\N- Private Kim Hyunsoo!
97 days.
Oh, 15 hours.
No, 15 hours.\N30 minutes are left!
Still?
Yes, right.
What's wrong with this?
Okay, the draw has begun!
The first lucky number is 39.
What's the second\Nlucky number?
36.
Damn, I got two right.
Here's a draw for the 3rd number.
3!
Yes, 3...\NThe 4th lucky number.
30.
There are a lot of numbers with 3 letters?
The 5th lucky number is 1!
So, what's the last 6th\Nlucky number?
The ball is spinning fast...
- Get rid of it.\N- Yes, sir!
What are you doing, not preparing for the roll call?
These guys just lost their themselves.
Don't you wake up?
Hey, hey ...
33!
Now, we'll draw a bonus ball for second place.
- The 934th.\N- Hey.
- I'll give you the lottery numbers.\N- What's wrong with him?
- //39, //30, //3\N- Probably spoiled milk.
You did.
Spoiled milk?
- What's wrong?\N- Are you crazy?
Drank spoiled milk?
Spoiled milk?
Crying while laughing.
Hey, go.
Excuse me, Sergeant Park. Are you okay?
No, because the world is so beautiful.
Yeah?
Hey, what are you saying?
I don't know.
5.7 billion.
South Korean soldiers.Hello.
How hard is it to work on the front desk all day and night?
We, the guards,
are here with warm love and consideration from the awe-inspiring Commander Comrade.
North Korean soldiers,
there's a weather forecast on the supercomputer of the Korea Meteorological Administration.
It will rain in three hours.
With the affection of our compatriots, we inform North Korea that there is no other supercomputer.
Hey, what are we gonna do about this?
According to our North Korean scientific satellite\NGwangmyeongseong No. 2.
It's not raining.
Our comrade fart man(Bang Kwi Nam) soldier leader and I
have developed a lot of feelings in such a program,
he has no taste and dryness, his name is also very rustic,
we have prepared three lines of poetry for comrade fart man, you wanna hear it?
IU from North Korea prepared an acrostic poem.
Of course I'll have to hear it.
Fart, farting boom boom.
Kwi, Kwi-nam.
Nam, South Korean hot pants.
Hot pants..
Comrade Yeonhee, take it easy.
Since IU sent us an acrostic poem.
I should send you a reply with an acrostic poem.
I know.
IU is the most beautiful singer in South Korea.
Should I say the first letter?\NAh.
She still think
she's pretty.
Yoo, I'm sorry to hear that.
Sergeant Park!
A South Korean soldier who only judges people by their looks.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
You're very angry.
But even angrier if you heard this?
That's what, 10 years of military service?
What should I do?\NI'm about to be discharged.
Where's medicine.
unable to get rid of the nasty sickness.
If you play around like that,
you're likely to end up in an acorn.
Irrational madness.\NThat's it. Come on!
Come on!
- It's not a coincidence.\N- Loyalty!
What's
that?
I think our GP has soldiers of interest.
Soldiers of interest?
Sergeant Park Chun-woo is a bit weird these days.
Park Chun-woo?
A real rich man doesn't ignore others.
A positive attitude of keeping dignity.
That's the real elite.
It's a good story.
Well, can I go to the bathroom?
Why are you asking me that?\NAsk your old man.
It's not small, it's big.
You're doing a good job.\NYou're not supposed to hold back your shit.
No!
What am I supposed to do?
Welcome, Comrade Lee Yongho.
What are you looking at?
I am just bored watching the German War movie.
Watch it together?
I've memorized everything now.
I should've seen this more than 100 times.
Chol-jin companion.
Can I ask you something?
I don't know anyone else, but I have to help Lee Yong-ho.
I picked up a piece of South Korean paper.
You know what this is?
It's called 645.
645?
If you get 6 correct out of 45 numbers,
A vicious capitalist exploitation technique
that fleeces the Korean people in the name of giving them huge amounts of money.
But this is the day of the last drawing.
Is this the latest piece of paper?
Just for fun, take a look.
OK.
Okay, there it is. .
Number one, three, and thirty.
3...
33, 36.
Lastly, number 39.
This is the number one.
What's the matter, Comrade Chol Jin?
It's...
What is this?
Yeah, well...
What should we do?
Yeah?
I almost broke my back.
The temperature is 21 degrees Celsius and the wind is from the northeast.
The wind speed is 14 m /s\NA lottery ticket weighs 75 grams.
If you plug in the formula for free fall.
The flight distance of Lotto is 1.23 km.
This is where the lottery is.
What's going on?
What?
Just hand out the flyers!
Oh.
Hello, here.
Put the gun down.
I'm not gonna eat you. Okay?
Come on.
Put the gun down.
What's your name?
It's Park Chunwoo?
My name is Lee Yongho.
Sergeant Lee Yongho.
It's been three days since we met.
I came out to meet my South Korean soldier.
Welcome to Free Korea.
What are you talking about, you stupid?
But why do you keep talking informally?
I mean you.
Do you know the game called "645"?
Out of 45 numbers, if you get 6 correct, you'll get 1st place.
I picked up a 645.
This is a piece of paper for first place.
So..
I'll give you 10% if you bring the cash.
I finally found it, thank you!
Hey, North Korean soldier.
That, that's mine.
So give it to me while I'm being nice.
What?
Is this yours?
Yeah, that's how I got here.
Stupid.
934th, right?
- Yeah.\N-1, 3, 30.
Number 33, number 36, number 39, right?
Yeah, so it's mine! Give it back!
You Korean boy think I'm hot pants?
And where does this note belong?
Who got it who's the owner.
What does that mean?\NWhat's that?
Sergeant Park Chun-woo.
When is your next shift again?
- What's that?\N- Answer me, you jerk!
Three days later, you punk!
I'll see you here in three days.
I'm gonna talk to you here again, okay?
Wait.
It hurts a lot?
No.
Are you... At night..
Did you meet a ghost and wrestled?
No.
But why do you walk around at night like a madman?
And in a minefield you'll find if you go in.
Wouldn't it be nice if you didn't explode?
You cross the bars and you're in the brig by law.
But you'll be discharged in a few months
and you have serious mental health problems.
I'm alright.
No problem at all.
But why cross the barbed wire every night like a madman.
Wandering around the Demilitarized Zone, you punk!
Five of the dog holes you dug!\NWho are you?
Really son of bitch?
Are you a spy? Nasty bastard.
I'm not a spy.
Don't you dare talk back to me, boy!
I'll report to the main office first\NGo to the hospital for treatment first.
Actually, I won first prize in the lottery.
I was watching TV in the Home Office.
Number 1, 3, 30, 33\NNumber 36 and 39.
The prize money alone is 5.7 billion won.
That lottery was brought to me by the battalion leader in the Jeep.
He didn't give it to me. It came like fate.
The recruits on duty together suddenly had diarrhea, and the ticket flew away.
- Is that gone?\N-yeah!
- So?\N- Well, so...
So, go back a little, huh?
Let me talk freely, huh?
- The lottery flew to the north.\N- Yes, yes
A North Korean soldier named Sergeant Lee Yongho picked it up.
I'm Captain Kang, 437\NPut me through to the hospital.
No, no, Chief.
- A few days ago, at the Military Demarcation Line.\N- Yes.
I met the North Korean soldier.
But the guy only wants to give me 10%.
That's a shame! That's mine.
It's yours, so it's not making sense.\NRight?
Do you have a helicopter now?\NWe have a critical patient. We need to get him out of here.
No, we were supposed to meet the North Korean soldier in three days...
Now the hole's blocked up. I can't see him.
The dog holes are blocked up.
It must have been hard?
Can you at least send a truck if the ambulance can't stop?
Look at my eyes.
Yeah?
We're going to the hospital. Hurry up.
No.
- I know I can't do that.\N- What?
Look.
I told you it's true.
I won 5.7 billion in the lottery!
Loyalty! TOD observation soldier\NPrivate First Class Kim Man-Cheol!
I need to talk to my leader.
You're just in time.\NYou use your computer a lot, don't you?
Can you use TOD to detect fake photos?
Computers have nothing to do with TOD.
This guy's good. He faked a photo, huh?
Let's go back. There's another one.
5.7 billion in North Korea?
Sergeant Park.
So you risked your life over the fence?
You're really incredible.
Hey, I'm glad I found it.\NIt's heaven's help
This secret is carried to the end of the grave.
- Yes.\N- Yes.
In all battles, power analysis is the basic.
If you know your enemy and know us, you'll win every battle.
What kind of guy is that North Korean guy who picked up the lottery?
A bastard.
Bastard?
Yes.
For the sake of the party and the people.
I thought this money should be spent for the country, of course.
Same.
What have the party and the state done for us?
You're right.
I wholeheartedly agree with Comrade Lee Yong-ho.
Hard parents,
my sister wants to be a singer's dream,
I will achieve in the end.
I have to change my dad's dentures first.
Very steel alloy\NSwiss dentures.
Change them all.
Chol Jin superior soldier comrade.
This heart must not change.
Whatever it takes to kick that Korean son of a bitch's ass.
Make sure you get back from your mission.
You know I have a daughter, right?
Doesn't have a piano that everyone else have.
I came home one day.
She drew the piano on the drawing paper with colored pencils.
Sola Sola Redo.
Can I give you 10%?
One day my wife is going to
pay my mother's medical bills
I'm going to put mom in a nursing home,
but I don't have the money or the piano.
One day the kid said,
Dad, why don't we have money?
Can I give you 15%?
With generous support and sponsorship for 15% of the shares, there is no better platoon leader.
Sergeant Park Chun-woo.
I'm a man of conscience, huh?\NLet's do it well.
Manchul, what number do you like?
Number? Maybe, 7?
- Ok, give you 7%\N- 10.
So the number 10, 10.
Come to think of it, isn't that a nice, perfect number?
Ten. Name is Ten. Ten. Ten
10, Ten.
Sergeant Park! Park...
What? Why is this open?
I think this is a supply tube.
The pipes are so old that they are often unclogged.
There is no ice in the demilitarized zone even in winter.
Only the supply officer knows the map of the springs and Wells.
How nice would it be to open up and talk?
On the south side is the Lost Property Act.
I mean, there's all kinds of weird stuff going on.
See, section four of the Lost Property Act.
When picking up something lost by another.
Compensation ranges from 5 percent to 20 percent.
How great would that be?
According to the law, you can claim compensation.
Is that so?
So I'm 80, you're 20.
Get out.
You really don't understand the language.
You'll need an ID to get that.
And even if you hold it, you wouldn't get any prize money!
It is said that the period to collect the bonus is one year.
You think there's nothing we can do?
Search all defectors whose in-laws and relatives have settled in the south.
We can find it, too. We win.
You don't make any sense. Negotiations are broken.
You bas...\NReally...
How did it go?
Where are those Korean motherfuckers?
If we search the defectors carefully.
We can find it, too.\NCan't we threaten him?
If you read that right.
I wouldn't have anything to say right now if you were sentenced on the spot.
Comrade political instructor.
Put the gun down.
Where do you want to go?
Yoduk political prison camp? Gaechon camp?\NPick one.
That's where people used to sweat and bleed.
The exploiters and the sectarians have come together.
It's like coming back to home. Very warm.
I'll tell you the truth, political instructor.
Not long ago Comrade Li Yongho.
Picked up a lottery ticket blown by the wind from Korea.
What's that?
I hear they give you a lot of money if you win.
- The Korean people's...\N- son of...
Political instructor comrade, the 645 won the first prize.
The Korean kid who claimed 645 was his.
We're negotiating a 50-50 split.
How much is the bonus?
The total amount is 5.7 billion won.
How much dollar.
In dollar terms...
6 million.
What? 6 million?
How much money are they gonna give us?
It must be 900,000.
Told us to eat 100,000.
No,10...\NI'm really speechless.
Aren't they thieves?
You think the north-south issue is that simple?
They always use brinkmanship.
The negotiations have broken down.\NWhat should we do now?
Negotiations are meant to be made up before fight.
We're gonna have to reconnect.
Does that give us an answer?
Meeting is a precious thing.
How earnestly are we waiting to meet?
The depression of not having an answer is really overwhelming.
I would like to speak to my compatriots in the North who do not sleep at night.
Kiha & The Faces.
Let's meet now.
Uh, warden, there, there..
I've seen it too, punks.
There must be a new number of people.
People?
What's wrong with them?
It looks like Korean consonants.
Korean initial consonants?
Yes.
Korean initial consonants? That's "k" in Korean. "K" in Korean.
Oh, right, right, right.
That, that k, d.
Yes!
- Hey, man, Manchul, you write it down.\N- Yes.
"K" and "S".
I, I.
- Is it Chi?\N- Right, right, right
Why do you keep rubbing your butt?
If it's "k" and "d", then "military"?
Chief, you're right.
Army, yes, you and I are the same army, army!
What about "K" and "S"?
Military?
Military.
Army, military.\NWe're getting in, all right?
After then?
Together?
Yeah?
Courtship?
A, Prison?
Like a dog bird?
A joint chest gay?
High-dap chest muscles?
You really have a poor imagination...
Co-parasitic fruit..
Hey, is that imagination?\NLonely death zone.
- Together?\N- Wait a minute
Why? What's wrong?
Who's in our GP that can go in and out of the Demilitarized Zone at will?
What, the water supply officer with the key to the gate?
Then they have a supply tube, right?
That's it.
Don't they have to bring water from somewhere in the winter?
- That's right.\N- That's right.
Here's the place they were talking about.
Common.
Water supply.
District.
JSA Common Water supply area.
Hey, give me the medicine that the supply officer drew.
Ah? You want me to look through it?
Look with your heart and you'll find it.
Heart?
I'm really going crazy.
Hey, where are you going?
A single stroke between controls.
You're not a chicken head, are you?
Drop the gun.
So before we get to the talks,
According to the principles of the UN Command,
Weapons will be collected separately.
Good.
It's like our military academy.
The lost and Found Act is bullshit.
I'm here to sternly correct a thief who went mad after eating it.
It's not 645, it's the lottery.
You have to be clear about that..
Don't use USA language.
This is not Korean land.
Let me ask you a question.
Do you know what the taxes are on the lottery?
Tax?
I knew this would happen.\NFor a skilled TA.
In the future.
The total winnings amount to N5.765772,844 won.
Up to 300 million won, 20 percent of other income tax and 2 percent of N resident tax will total 22 percent.
Over 300 million won, other income tax is 30 percent\Nand resident tax is 3 percent, or 33 percent.
The actual amount received, excluding income tax and residential tax, is
3,914,959,762 won.
You don't even know that.
What about 80% and what about 90%?
Show us, comrade Choljin.
What is it? Lunch boxed meal?
It's just a strong point that's easy to recognize.
Strong point?
Yanks call them PowerPoint?
Our People's Army is beyond words.
I just need one shot of drawing.
Why bother to talk like that and look good?
We didn't budge an inch in our opinion,
so you know what?
What if we don't take it?
Then I have nothing to say.
Get up, everybody.
Here we go again!
Brinkmanship again.
In that case, do you think we'd be scared?
And why do you own the lottery?
You won't get the prize with it anyway.
Do you know where to find the prize money?
Is it not looking at the co-op?
Agricultural cooperatives.
Uncle, we're not a co-op.
The Agricultural Cooperative is at the bank. The bank.
Eight to two? That's a lot of concessions.
Did you learn to eat for free from American wolves?
Do you run the lottery?
This is property issued by the Republic of Korea.
You are illegally occupying our property, do you understand that?
What do you suggest?\NIllegal possession?
You're lucky you didn't go to the Azzo coal mine.
Azzo coal mine?
You punk!\NAre you done talking?
Yeah, I'm done. Why?\NWhat are you gonna do?
Scoundrels.
I was going to make it good, but it didn't work!
What if I don't do well?\NAre you trying to do it or what?
You punks!
We don't need any money!
I'm gonna burn that guy's 645.\NI'm gonna burn him up!
- I'm gonna burn it\N- Burn it!
Those guys could really burn up.
I feel depressed too.
I've never seen such an ignorant person.
Let's just, let's just do what they say.
Hey, how can you say that?
That's ours. Why is it 10% of ours?
All I have to do is get the lottery back.
Think about it.
We have the ticket. What are they gonna do?
Yeah, that's the right answer.
Mr. Political instructor, are you really gonna burn 645?
So we don't need the money either?
So what do we do?
Are you asking me to bow down to those useless guys?
I should have taken 10%.
Isn't that a lot of money for us?
8 : 2!\NWe won't budge any more!
Fxxk 8:2.\N7:3.
Who take the 7.
Of course you.
Did you say we're 7?
Considering North Korea's difficult economic situation.
We made a decision for the greater good.
Is it true?\NIs that a fake account?
So.
Can we at least write up an agreement?
Of course we do.
The 645 agreement.
Clause 1.
The winning sum is Democratic People's Republic of Korea take 7\NIn proportion to the Republic of Korea take 3.
Clause 2, even in the event of a natural disaster.
Clause 3, if there is a dispute between the two Koreas.
The International Court of Justice of the United Nations\Nis a court of exclusive jurisdiction.
Clause 4, two copies of the agreement.
The north and the south keep one copy after signing and sealing.
Remember, it's either 7-3 or war.
Just trust me for once for the sake of national prosperity.
Wait.
Just saying.
What happens if you do not pay
after we give 645?
Those sons of bitches.
Is that why we're making a 7-3 offer?
That's what he was thinking.
Put down.
You got to let it go, stupid.
I told you to let it go.
I told you.
If you don't let go on the count of three.
I'm gonna rip your teeth out.
OK.
Do it.
1!
2!
- 3!\N- 3!
- Hurry up and find the lottery! Come on!\N- Take 645 away! 645!
You sons of bitches!\NI'm gonna shoot you!
- Shoot me! Bastard! Shoot!!!!\N-Manchul, where are you?
Turn off the lights! Turn off the lights!
It's because I know where it is when it'sound.
- Move...\N- You out of your mind?
- Chief, where are you?\N- Don't look for me, man!
- Wait, wait, wait...\N- Come here.
Eyes, eyes, eyes...
- Stupid.\N- Stupid.
- Bring it on .\N- What are you doing here?
Just turn on the light, but it's dark. Did you see anything?
These unnatural and helpless feelings.
Good.
Here, take a picture.
A little bit over here.
Good.
Isn't that the South Korean supply officer?
Ah, ah!\NWhat are you doing here?
Didn't we have a blockage in the water line before?
I helped a lot back then.
What's this?
I've heard about what's going on.
Sergeant Park, how much did you pay for it?
I didn't.
Didn't?
Just picked it.
- Hey, this...\N- Hey, be quiet!
What? Pick up?
Even your kids pick it up and you are claiming it?
You son of a bitch!
Well, I think...
Because it's something that no one can claim.
It's the Peace lottery.
How about a 50-50 split?
Five to five, we're good.
A clean 50-50 split, huh?
Good!
All right, I got it.
But it's not over yet.
The north gives the South a lottery.
I think the South will get the first prize back.
But we have to transfer the money north again.
But how are we supposed to trust each other?
How about this?
It's like a prisoner swap in a spy movie.
The duration is 1 week.
The North pays the lottery and the south gets its money back
Before handing over the change to the North again.
One soldier from the north and one from the south.
That should do.
Who's gonna go?
All right, whoever goes!
In case of emergency.
How do you get in touch?
My waist...
You're alive.
This is an ancient emergency network issued in this common water area since the Korean War.
The cell phone of TA-312 A.K.A. Daughter.
But both North and South Korea.
There should be a phone somewhere in GP.
Manchul, where are you from?
Cheongdam-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul.
I am also of the old school in Seoul.
Sergeant Park, you're from Gangwon-do?
Gangwon-do is not the same Gangwon-do.
It's completely different from North Korea.
Why don't I take the post?
Manchul is not part of our unit.
He was assigned to the TOD observation corps.
Yeah right.
Just 1 week.
But that's not supposed to work, is it?\NHow do I get to North Korea?
Let's play rock paper scissors.
Manly, just one round!
No, Sergeant Park.\NWhat kind of rock-paper-scissors...
Hurry up and play rock paper scissors.\NRock paper scissors. Rock paper scissors.
- Just one round.\N- Just one round
Yeah just one round.
- Hurry up!\N- Yes.
Rock paper scissors.
Wait a minute. Just once.\NWhat? The third round!
Sergeant Park, what's wrong with you?
- Manchul, I'm sorry.\N- It's the last time.
- Where is that? Really?\N- Just one round, just one round.
If I lose this time, I'll really go.\NJust one more round, huh?
It's really the last round!
Yes, just one round!\NI'm really going to go.
Hey, I'm sorry. N-Last, last.
You do it. Rock, paper, scissors.
Yes.\NRock-paper-scissors paper!
Sergeant Park, this is fate.
Punks.
Hey, I didn't do it right!
I'm watching what you guys usually do.
Let the sweat run like a river.
If you roll your eyes like that, does your body flutter?
- Be loyal! Be loyal!\N- Impossible.
There was no place to hide from the sight of our fellow security instructors.
Hey, you!
Rack your brains.
It's about to be executed. We should do something about it.
Even though we sleep under the same quilt in the same housekeeping class.
I wonder who is guarding the comrade instructor's lackey.
Where we can deceive fellow security instructors in our posts.
Not a single place.
There is a place.
The only place we can escape the murderous gaze of our instructor.
Do you know what the most recognized ant is?
Labor ants.
A calf has only one life, and producing milk is also a battle.
Milk 100 kilos a day.
Be the best working cow in the Republic, you know?
Comrade Yeon-hee,\NWhen did you come?
Comrade Youngchul! Why are there wild boars?
Lost Amy near the army not long ago.
I saw him crying, so I picked him up.
Does he have to be fed to eat, too?
In the demilitarized zone.
Don't wild boar and red deer make good egg fillings?
Actually, I'm a little upset.
Could something this beautiful eat me?
Just a month, and you can grow a little more
Brother! Brother!
What?
Here.
What are you doing with your head?
Hey, recruit.\NPut it up there.
What? I didn't hear you!
I said lift it up!
Don't use your hands! Lift up the rope!\NPulled tight!
I was scared at first.
It was a terrible time. It was a terrible time.
Because of the softness...
- Recruit!\N- Private Kim Hyunsoo.
Bring me a glass of water.
You made a joke.
But it's not fun, huh?
What's the word used in South Korea at times like this?
That's what I did earlier.
- Gap, Gapbungyo? Gapbungyo.\N- Gapbungyo.
It's a sudden chill!
Gapbungyo is all of a sudden, the atmosphere is like the principal!
I'm gonna die comrade!
Again!
Comrade Li Yongho, let's do it again.
What's the point of Moonsong?
I'm sorry I was born liberal arts.
Good.
Next, Honbabian.
Honbabian...
Who eats alone?
Good job. What's a Honkono?
Who goes to coin karaoke alone?
Good.
Now.
What's bondalbonjum?
Stir-fry the chrysalis...
Bondalbonjum!
If you ask for a number, I'll give you a number!
I'm gonna die!
That's it, this life is end, this life is end.
Really, really, that's really, really.
Masang.
- Heartbreak\N- My beloved people all over the country.
Brave men and women of the People's Army, brothers and sisters.
Dear, dear nation,\NDear nation.
If the people's army of the Republic must recite a New Year message.
Memorize it vigorously.
The beloved people of the whole country.
Brave men and women of the People's Army,\Nbrothers and sisters.
Sergeant Park, put your hat on.
It's a good match.
Go as a private first class. What?
Can you believe it?
We're all in this together now.
How can you not drink on a happy day like today?
Comrade Choljin!
Prepared the republic's most delicious rhododendron wine!
I knew this would happen, which is why we've got drinks and food.
I only prepared the most popular items of PX in the Republic of Korea.
Okay, just a little bit more of the heavy flavor.
Tie it up.
DUDUDU.
Now it's important. You watch it.
Turn this end
around!
This is what makes tired soldiers want to eat.
Taste it again.
Give it to me.
Let's have a candid conversation.
It's all here. You know who's got the biggest ball?
This is the bomb shelter.\Npublic water supply area.
Stay.
There is Panmunjom in North Korea and Peace House in the south.
Then here.
This is the back door to peace.
The back door to peace?
Is this make sense?
This is the back door to future peace.
Let's have a toast.
- Come on, cheers\N- Cheers!
Good!
- My, my !\N- My turn! My! My!
Hey, you just crossed the bridge.
What did you say? The guy up there dumped you.
Why are you so surprised?
Is that how the South Korean president walked through Panmunjom?
Okay, so our aggregate score is 1-0.
- Now switch places.\N-Nice.
Ah wait.
Do you really want to change this?\NThis is North Korea.
Have you been crying all night?\NSkip!
Okay, let's skip it.
Go, go.
Ok ! Ok ! Focus!
It's okay.\NYou're in the brig.
But how old are you?
In North Korean terms, I'm 29.
I'm 32 years old.
It's the big brother. You can speak freely.
Ok? Let's get a cup from my brother.
Yes, brother.
But it seems your birth declaration was a lot late?
I did it in time.
What does Sergeant Park Chun-woo want to do when you become rich?
I'm gonna start a farm. A cow farm.
I graduated from the Department of Animal production.
A dairy farm?
Cows are pregnant for life to be milked.
How inhumane.
So I've decided.
Cows need postnatal conditioning, too. I'm gonna start that farm.
What will Corporal Lee Yong-ho do when you become rich?
I have a lot of work to do.
I want to buy a watch for dad.
And my beautiful sister who sings well...
Sister? Do you have a beautiful sister?
Brother!\NWhat are you saying?
South Korean television, the Internet.
What scheming has been done to our republic there?
You're supposed to be watching all day.
It's like me. I use my monitor all day.
Of all the networks and TV shows, do you know girl groups?
No, you didn't know that, did you?
Stop it, comrade Choljin!
What are you doing?
Hey, Seungil! Choi Seungil!
You stupid.
You've heard the American Yankee water?
Did you go to a thought struggle?
Comrade Political Instructor.
Hey, Seungil.
Please play it again Yongho.
- What?\N- Play it!
I love you.
Rollin' Rollin' Rollin'\NRollin' Rollin' Rollin'
What are you all doing?Get out of here!
Let's do it together! Let's do it together!
Let's overcome the hardships and build a better garden!
With a great general, we'll win!
Because of the nature of GP work,
Once deployed, no one can go outside for three months.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You have to get sick to get out.
I thought a lot about it.
Drink stale milk a year out of date.
Food poisoning?
But the way to get out of cleanly.
Whether it's your right arm or your left arm, only one of your arms is broken.
You can get out.
Pick one that you want.
What would hurt the least?
It's going to hurt.
I've already told you about it.
As soon as you get out, you'll be taken to the N.K. Capital Hospital.
You're just gonna get a month's cast, all right?
Loyalty!
- This?\N- No, no.
Then, with this?
No, why...
Okay, take it easy.
- This, this...\N- A hammer?
Yeah, it's one shot.
Stone. That sounds clean.
Oh.
With small stone?
No, this, this, this.
Tell my mom I love her.
OK.
Sorry.
1, 2!
Where are you going to keep the lottery?
I'll keep it in my wallet.
You don't know anything about people.
What if a thief stops us?
So I'm ready.
I was gonna talk back to you.
I always thought a zipper would be better.
He was a revolutionary soldier in white with a single shot.
An unbeatable army!
Strength of steel! The vigorous Brawler!
A lightning charge into the enemy's fortress.
One man can ruthlessly defeat hundreds of enemies.
The attacking spirit of a hundred is special defeat.
This time the training.
Put the granite on the lower abdomen, with the big view far value of a hit immediately hit the training.
I hear there's a new assignment this time, right?
Who?
The recruit!
Out.
In an indomitable revolutionary spirit.
Give Dantian a little strength.
Hit rocks with little belly!
The beloved people of the whole country.
Brave officers and men of the People's Army, brothers and compatriots.
Today we all work hard and meaningfully.
What they've done this past year to be proud of.
Isn't this a New Year message from our comrade Chairman?
Have you learned all this by heart?
What are you guys still doing? Why don't clap, clap!
Okay, you need to wake up.
- Welcome to a hopeful New Year!\N- Got it. Wake me up.
What happens when you get hurt?
If you get hurt, just put on a big sauce, otherwise you'll get smashed.
Stop it!\NStop it now!
What are you doing?
Comrade political instructor, we are conducting basic military education and training.
The recruit was assigned to the farm!
We don't need a drill!
Is that so?
What's this?
Hey, recruit.
Private Kim Hyunsoo.
Hey, hey, get out, get out.
I told you I had to do it by today, right?
- Sorry.\N- Sorry?
Really...
- Stupid.\N- It's just...
New boy, let's go smoke.
Out!
You bring Masang?
Are you hurt.
No.
Really?
Really, for real.
It's okay. Yeah.
Don't think of this life as a failure.\NIt's all small but certain happiness.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
You're not part of our unit.
Give me.
How can you spit on it?
It's so hard.
Stop it. Just.
That's amazing.
You didn't use shoe polish, but it's glossy.
What's your secret?
What's the secret..
In life, there's a guy who doesn't want to waste his shoe polish.
Now, spit it out.
What's wrong with your tone?
Did you sprain your leg?
You must have sprained your leg, it hurts.
I don't know anything. I miss my mom every night.
So you're an animal doctor.
I heard what Comrade Lee Yongho said about 645.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask me, okay.
What about Korea?
Don't look down on me.
Go away! A duck that can't even lay an egg.
Can't ducks lay eggs?
I don't know what the problem is. It's not breeding well.
The farm thrives when eggs are hatched and young are born.
Looks like I came to the right guy.
I majored in animal production and mating.
Atmosphere is important when it comes to breeding success.
Atmosphere?
You have to respect her personal life.
The partitions and lighting should also be emotional.
It would be better if there was music\Nlove songs and stuff like that.
There's one of my favorite songs.
It's that song.
- Live with the moon and stars.\N- Live with the moon and stars.
- Paradise of feeling.\N- Paradise of feeling.
- You live with me\N- You live with me
- This earnest heart\N- This earnest heart
Comrade Yeon-hee.\Nwelcome.
Comrade Youngchul, how have you been?
It's long, but who is this ggonsam?
I'm Choi Jung-nam, a newly assigned farm management soldier.
You two say hello.
Good night..
Stop moving! Stop moving!
It's a mine.\NEverybody back off.
You, you! Don't move!\NDon't move, you punk!
Contact the home squadron! Contact the demining team!
- Yes, sir!\N- Yes, sir!
Then it'll be late.
Everyone, step aside.
- This is what we planted.\N- No...
It's a wooden-box mine planted by North Korea.
- The radius of the kill is 3m.\N- Get back off!
About 5m?
It explodes when you step on it or open the lid.
Remove the safety pin before opening the lid.
It was like I'm in a detached situation.
Yeah?
After eating 100 sweet potatoes, I was really depressed.
Everybody on the ground!
- Get down!\N- Get down!
Get down!
Get down?
- Applause!\N- Applause!
It's a miracle, Comrade!
One night, you're gonna have to pack 100 eggs.
The duckling lays one egg every 10 minutes.
Rabbit, pig, you're going crazy.
The food problem in our republic has finally been solved!
Wow, you just showed up?
It will come at a time of hardship when millions of people starve to death.
What took you so long to show up?
Comrade Choi Jeong-nam.
You're a nation's talent that comes out once in a thousand years!
No.
I recommend Comrade to the cadre training school at once!
Battalion commander, Battalion commander comrade!
Comrade Choi Jung Nam is a rookie who just got assigned to the squad.
- There's still a lot to learn..\N- Shut up!
It's already decided. Send him to a senior training school right now.
What do you mean by going to a school?
There is a military academy in South Korea, but there is no military academy in North Korea.
If anyone gets a letter of recommendation,
You're chosen to go to a training school for cadres.
When?
You're leaving the day after you got the letter of recommendation.
Where?
Where else to go? Pyongyang.
Congratulations. I've never been there before in my life.
Wake up!
That's the only car you can drive.
How's it going?
I don't know what it is, but I got it all back.
I got rid of it.
The repairs will take at least three or four days.
- The...\N- Go for broke..
Well done.
Let's go. There won't be a miracle, will there?
Listen to what I'm saying.
That being the case, you crossed the line.
I want to go home.
Do you know what Pyongyang is?
Places you can't go if you want to.
Comrade Chunwoo, take this opportunity to change your fate.
I want to go home.
Why?
Make the carts and the ducks fly?
I'm screwed.
Loyalty!\N437 Cheif, Kang Eunpyo!
Where you can't even get an ant near you...
Where?
Who do you mean?
Heroic soldiers who give themselves to remove mines!
Where!
That, Sergeant Ha...
Did the G.P. Experience soldier go on duty?
In the dining room.
To the dining!
Stand at attention!\NAbout Captain..
Sit down and eat.
Is it him?
Excellent. That's the soldier.
I have a good hunch.
Is it you?
The soldier you removed the mines and saved the lives of your comrades?
Yeah?
Department, department, official...
- Attention.\N- Right.
You really enjoyed your meal.
Well, is there anything about military life that's inconvenient?
- Yeah.\N- Yeah?
Ok, where is your hometown?
Up there, Ham...
Ham? Ham?
Ham? Ham where?
It's Hamburg.
Hamburg?
Germany's Son Heung-min SV... Hamburg?
Yes.
The model soldier I've been looking for is right here, huh?
A true soldier who gave up his foreign nationality to fulfill his noble military duty!
Yeah, well, what's your resolution?
He gave up his foreign nationality and tried to become a Korean soldier.
Tell me!
In German.
German...
Comrade Lee Yongho, one in a million.
I wish I didn't have to use this.
I've memorized everything now.
You should've seen this more than 100 times.
I am a Korean.
Did you understand?
Yes.
Translate.
Give up German citizenship and choose Korean citizenship.
It's not anything special, right.
Because you only get one chance to defend your country.
The most advanced guard task that no one can complete.
I had the confidence that I could do anything.
If you ask me why, I'm just gonna say this.
I am a proud Korean.
Brother...
Stand up!
Applause! Applause!
That's right! That's right!
Hey, this is a moving eco-friendly car.
Upload by adm820@gmail.com
Stop! Stop!
This is by order of the Legion's political department
They postponed the transfer of Choi Jung-nam to an executive school.
Film the revolutionary recipe for increasing food production.
All outposts have priority spread!
I submitted the plan to the Legion's political department.
I used a little trickery.
Thanks.
It's all I can give you.
Make no mistake, this is all because of me.
Comrade Youngchul told me, you don't have to worry.
Hey, I'm curious. Can I ask you something?
- Of course.\N- Wouldn't it be...
You know that fart guy?
It's that guy.
Every time I'm on the air, I'm gonna break your mouth.
When I see a guy that good-looking.
Break his leg.
You can jump rope with a rubber band on.
Never get too close to this unbeatable bastard.
Yes.
What many people want to know is this.
That's why mating is so combative.
Please introduce the special secret of Comrade Choi Jeong-nam.
To increase milk production from cows.
The important thing is to rub it.
Wipe! Is friction more important than anything else?
Just pinch the breast of the cow like this.
Use stroking to relieve accumulated chest muscles.
Come on, everybody, look this way. Come on, squeeze like this.
Hold it like this.
Like this?
- From the top...\N- Show me.
Stop eating.\NYou're going to become a real pig.
Pig..
You're good.\NGood, meticulous.
The chickens on our farm laid 645 eggs this morning.
Very good news.
What's the secret to success in this battle?
Love.
It was love.
Yes, it is love.
What, love?
I'm gonna go out.
Yeonhee, I...
Lee Yongho?
Seohyeon Station on the Bundang Line.
The moment you get out of the Armed Forces Capital Hospital,\Nyour life-long mission begins.
Take the subway.
The subway is the safest.
And don't make eye contact with anyone.
Don't ever.
Get in.
Guard officer, you wanted to see me?
Hey, Yeonhee, sit.
I called you because I wanted to talk to you.
Is there anything inconvenient about the work of the Corps propaganda team?
Let me know
if you do.
No, I'm happy with it
What is this?
This is an oil lotion I bought with dollars not long ago.
It smells so good. I think of Comrade Yeonhee
Oh, and I bought a nice bottle of wine.
It's ok.
And there is no reason to receive such a gift from a comrade security instructor.
Why do you keep doing this? Didn't you say you were gonna help me?
Don't!
You girl don't understand me?
You seem to watch a lot of movies, guard officer.
What?
That's what they do to make people fall in the movies.
Can women do this?
But movies and reality are different.
At the outpost of the revolution.
You are so partisan.
Yeonhee!
Bearing the heavy responsibility of national reunification
An elite member of the legion Propaganda team!
It hurts.
Are you gonna make me look like some asshole in heat?
What age is it now, God damn it.
What the hell are you doing here?
Yeah, I'm just passing through...
Let's have a cup of coffee. Let's go.
Yes.
There are brokers in front of the head office of the Agricultural Cooperative.
The winner will be subject to a tax deduction of around 30%.
These brokers do it to launder money
After deducting about 20 percent of the funds, they propose cash transaction.
But they're all liars.
If he gets caught, he might just take the lottery.
You have to watch out for the brokers.
If you go to the bank, go to the petition police immediately.
There's a special elevator that lotto winners can take.
Go to the police and take the elevator.
That's it. That's the end of it.
Come in.
Psycho soldier brother.
- What's up?\N- Come.
- Why are you doing this?\N- You have a daughter.
Do you understand the heart of parents?
- Psycho soldier!\N- What's wrong?
Ah!
Psycho soldier?
What's this?
Manchul? Why are you running away?
He hasn't found money yet?
What are you doing in Seoul?
Money, did you find the money?
Why aren't you picking up the phone?
You punk!
Aren't you answering the phone?
What should I do?
Let's go have a cup of stick coffee.
- Let's go.\N- Yes.
Choi Seungil, 645, 500,000.
Lee Yongho, 645. 750,000.
Choi Jung Nam on June 16th.
16th, no soldiers came in?
Our Republic's Hero.\NChoi Jung-nam, Comrade.
What are you saying? Is there anything uncomfortable?
No.
Comrade Choi Jeongnam. Where are you from?
Ham...
Ham, where?
It's Hamheung.
Nice to meet you.
I'm from Hamheung, too.
I'm also from Hamheung. What part?
I mean, um...
I thought you were the hero of the Republic of Korea.
But it turns out.
A traitor to the nation.
Get in.
Comrade Yeonhee, come here.
I found something interesting today.
Comrade Lee Yong-ho said that Comrade Yeon-hee was an enemy?
Yeah.
But our comrade Lee Yongho has not been seen recently.
Do you know Yeonhee?
Did he happen to cross the Military Demarcation Line?
Running south.
Comrade security instructor.
Who are you?
The hero of the Republic, Choi Jeong-nam, was a ghost from the beginning.
You bastard!\NWho are you!
I am proud
- Republic of Korea Army Sergeant\N- You son of a bitch!
Rebel of the Republic! South Korean reactionary spy!
Your face looks white and clean.
Ever since you started calling the balls.
- I asked around, you son of a bitch. - Calm down.
Bastard, I...
I'm gonna kill this bastard today! I'm gonna die, too!
Comrade Yeonhee, give me that gun.
Give me that gun!
Let go of this!
What's going on?
Comrade political instructor.
It's here.
We need to revise our plan and head south now!
Comrade political instructor.
I'll contact the south side. All right.
Move to the public water supply area now!
How are you going to get here?
When the guard instructor wakes up, one of them has to die!
Comrade Yeonhee.
I used to be a special instructor!
A special instructor who went all the way to the Middle East.
Don't worry.\NTake him
and go, quickly.
Oh...
- You have to go, you have to go!\N- Hey, wait...
Take it.
The situation is urgent, the identity of Chunwoo comrade was found.
Wait, wait.
Wait.
The young boar was in a lot of trouble.
Does the boar especially not follow you?
When you look at this handkerchief, you're bound to think of us.
On the way back, please let the boar return to its mother's arms.
Yeah.
Go easy, Comrade Jeongnam.
Quick go to! Don't get hurt! Go find Mom!
Go. There's no time.
Yeon-hee, is it ok that I'm going?
I'm fine. Just go.
Hello, Comrade Kim Kwang-cheol.
You have two choices.
A chance to enjoy good fortune after receiving a large sum of money.
Another is..
You and I are not getting away with this.
One of us
is gonna die here.
If you assemble the gun first, you're a dead man.
But you're really out of luck.
I was a member of the 525th Special Operations Group,\Npart of the Operations Directorate of the General Staff of Neray.
AK47, SR-25.
M9 Beretta, Glock 17.
I've won every fire I've touched in a while!
Is that so?
But I'm not gonna die under a gun.
38th Aviation Army Regiment under\Nthe Reconnaissance General Bureau of the People's Armed Forces.
I came from a sniper brigade.
Comrade Kim Kwang Cheol.
Choose well.
Quick.
Why are your hands so disobedient?
Okay, your exit pass to the Capital Hospital of the Founding Army.
Depart from Sohyeon Station on Bundang Line on 14:00.
Transfer to Line 3 at Seonneung Station, Line 2.
Transferred from Jongno 3-ga to Line 5 again.
Arrived at the Nonghyup headquarters at Seodaemun Station.
Good, very good.
By the way, 15:30\NAre you suddenly leaving the Nonghyup headquarters?
At 15:48. Buy and eat at Gwanghwamun.
Buy a lottery ticket at 16:01.
Eat soondae at Euljiro 3-ga.
Why do you buy a hot dog\Nand an Americano at Jonggak Station?
Why do you go to the playground after looking at the bicycle repair shop?
Yeah, 5 minutes ago. Hwangga's kalguksu.
You got caught.
Yes, it's a kalguksu restaurant.
Who?\NMr. Pervert?
Excuse me, is there a pervert among you?
Mr. Pervert Soldier!
You got a call. Please answer it.
Come on.
- Hello, communications security...\N- Hey, you punk!
Did you find the money at the bank?
Why are you angry? I got kicked out!
What?
Maybe, lottery?
- Is this the right place?\N- Yes, that's right.
Hey, Chunwoo.
- Brother!\N- Yeonhee.
- Comrade Yeonhee!\N- How did you know this place?
It's a long story.
You okay?\NAre you hurt?
- You okay?\N- Yes.
Seungil is late.\NWhat happened?
By the way, did you find the money?
Comrade Manchul is all right to come?
The fool.
I sent him to 645.
How dare you do this to my only sister?
You son of a bitch! Say it!
What trick did you do?\NTalk about it!
What's the matter, brother?
Comrade Lee Yongho! Calm!
I told you it wasn't like that!
Hyung? Why am I your Brother?
If you're a year older, you're older than me!\NSo you call me brother-in-law?
Brother-in-law?
You son of a bitch or an asshole?
Shit!
The client didn't do anything. What are you two doing?
I'm my idea whether you like me or not. I'm not a toy.
Yeah, well, if you take a closer look, they're all right.
Loosen the collar at once.
Thank you, Yeonhee.
Shut up!\NYou didn't do anything right either!
Yes.
- Kim Manchul!\N- Manchul!
Loyalty!
TOD Observation Soldier Kim Man-chul.
Mission accomplished, safe and sound.
Hey, how did you find this? I heard you couldn't get to the bank.
Isn't the first prize in this lottery paid out of the account?
So right from the start, you can cash it in a day.
It's an impossible plan.
The bonus wasn't actually drawn at the bank.
The prize money.
I was there to find him.
Mr. Rich Soldier, yes.
Don't you think the country got too much in taxes?
Yeah, that's crazy.
The civil servants.
I want to see something.
Yes?
The thing.
Not bad.
What you doing?
She said she wanted to see something.
Who said anything about wanting to see your stuff?
Things! The real thing! Cha! Why is that?
Are you out of your mind?
- Hands on pants...\N- No. no.
- No, no.\N- Are you crazy? People are so fucked up these days.
- No...\N- Hey, you pervert.
Enough is enough!\NPlease.
I put a zak here.
-Disgusting.\N-That psycho Kang Eun-pyo
- Let me.\N- Yes.
Do you know how nervous I get every time I go to the bathroom?
What if it gets wet?
If you lose and the bank doesn't pay you.
That is not.
It's not just money.
No, what's the point of giving four days and three nights off?
I'm coming to Seoul now.
What should I do when I come to Seoul?
All right! All right!
No, I'll show you everything.
No I don't want to.
- What's going on with this...\N- No, I don't look.
- No, close the ...\N- This is outrageous.
Does that make sense to you?
Why are you yelling at me?
Aunt Popeye at the South Gate loan shark?
What is Popeye?
Just eat spinach and his eyes roll.
American imperialist with his fists at will.
Popeye has a terrible name.
Yeonhee, Yeonhee,Yeonhee.
Don't move.
Back off!
Comrade security instructor!
It's made in America!
Four million dollars!
We can share this!
- Yeah.\N- Split it, you and me?
Why?
- Brother.\N- Comrade security instructor!
This is 645 of peace.
It's a sign from heaven that North and South Korea\Ncan share in peace and harmony.
Hello, Peace?
Are you still in a romantic mood?
What peace? Do you want to be beaten half to death?
One of two has to die!
Real peace came.
OK!
Stupid.
You think I don't know?
I know it all.
What are you doing?
That's our money. Put it down.
Stay!
What are you guys doing? Do something!
Okay, I'll kill you.
I'll kill you in one go.
Soldiers of the North and South, goodbye.
What's that?
Hey, you fucking boar! Stop!
Stop! Hey, boar!
Comrade Choljin, follow quickly!
Come here! Don't even eat that!
Hey, you boar!
My money!
Don't shoot me! It's me!
How's it going?
The mine exploded.
Comrade Guard instructor flew into the sky.
And the money?
The boar took it all.
It's all over.
Fxxk...
Brother.
It's all over.
He's 645.
It was ridiculous from the start.
Let's go back.
What the hell have we been doing?
Wait! Wait!
Hey what you doing now?
No, Sergeant Park! It's not like that. It's not like that.
- You son of a bitch.\N- Get your hands off me, Man-chul! Get your hands off me!
Yes, I want it down! I want it off!
Take it out! Take it out!
Done!
Huh? Why is that coming out there?
Mister, this, this, this.
Right, right.
Here?
- What's this?\N- Can you...
Right, right.
Manchul...
Manchul!
This, this.
I didn't put anything in bag.
I brought another $400,000 with me.
Manchul!
So this is reversed.
There's a twist!
Yes, yes.
Kim Man-chul is on a reward vacation right now!
Thanks.
Yeonhee.
- Chunwoo!\N- One, bucket plant, stone three, raccoon.
- Squid, beef soup, Turkey, octopus\N- How much?
Here's $400,000.
I was kind of... running over here.
But if it's $400,000 it's still a lot of money.
Of course. $400,000.
So if you split it in half, that's $200,000.
About 200 million won.
If it's 200 million to 15 percent.
30 million won?
I can pay the piano and pay my mother's medical bills.
But for that money you could buy100 false teeth made in Switzerland.
Are you gonna let me in, too?
Of course you do.
Yeonhee.
Don't forget my account number.
All right, I'll text you.
Comrade Chunwoo, good job these days. Goodbye.
Will we see each other again?
What are we gonna do when we meet again?
We can see each other when we're unified, right?
Right.
Let's all be united and pray.
Unification is nothing.
All you can see when you want to is unity.
Yeonhee.
Now it's time to leave.
Be safe.
Everything you do goes well, and make a lot of money.
Please grant your wish.
Make sure you open a farm.
There must be glory in all things.
I hope Yeon-hee can become a successful singer.
You must come to Pyongyang to eat cold noodles.
Don't get sick. Don't get sick.
Well, then go find yourself a good date.
And you.
Go!
Hello, members of the Korean Armed Forces.
This is the Broadcasting Bureau of the 24th Division of the Korean People's Army.
How's your day?
Turn around and turn right!
- Round and round and  right!\N- Turn around and turn right!
Turn around and turn right!\NTurn around and turn right!
But there are no surprises that fall short!
Come on, win the lottery!\NA thousand won lotto is just right!
- Congratulations congratulations,\N- Congratulations congratulations
Congratulations congratulations